So let's take the previously created method and take the situations and the condition at a low.
We start by this the atfirst method that we have seen and we have to create if had the equal.
What to know this condition new node dot next equal to new note node and they have refers to then you
note.
What does this mean if there is an empty list?
There is an empty link, a circle at list and we need to insert the first note inside it.
We create new note equaled next in the end of next, equal to a new node.
This is the note.
And it refers to itself because it is a circle circling it, blessed and the had equal to, then you
know it.
This is how we insert a first note and the circular link and let us do things that you should take heard
about it that if it is the only one that it contains inside that linked at least.
Inside the circle of Lincoln, this it should refer to itself.
And we should put the hat on a.
Had equal to then, you know, now let's see the other example, the other case if we have.
A link, at least, that contain one or more notes, then we should take that as a statement of this
method called at first.
OK.
We should take care about making a struct known equals temp equal to have.
And while temp next does not equal to, had we are searching about it, then it created temp temp equals
to that temp the next.
Then this would be removed and equal the temp next equal to the newly created node.
And new node next equal to the had and therefore it had equal to that.
You note, refer this copy the reference of the newly created node to the next node, which is 1024,
and change their 1024, the then the old node inside the linked list and change it to the newly created
one.
So therefore, we have inserted in, you know, at the beginning by making everything works fine and
ensure that all the references are working fine.
Time complexity of doing this insertion is best case is of one inserting the first note if there is
a link to the list, empty linked list and we are inserting the first note its best case because we
are doing a constant work inserting one note at the beginning of this list.
Worst case scenario is of often because we are inserting note in none empty list, because here we have
inserted.
Exactly.
We are inserting the note at the first position and that's making it constant war.
But the reference of the last note since it's circular list link, at least, that points to the first
one.
We should go to there through all the elements, through all the notes inside the circle or linked list
to get the last one and this last one, which should point to the first one.
This operation will give us a complexity of and depending on the number of nodes that it is contained
inside this circle or linked list.